Finding Aid for Robert C. Metcalf papers, 1950-2008
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Project Files
  - Projects by Job Number
    - Job No. 64-60, Dr. Lyle D. Elliott 1075 Chestnut Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1960
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 64-60 & 132-97, 4 12x12, 2 11x8, & 48 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum, pencil on tracing paper, colored pencil on paper; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide boxes 2 & 6)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Professor Peter Hinman and Ms. Elizabeth Young (Job 132-97) Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 65-60, Professor and Mrs. Kenneth Case 1021 Chestnut Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1960
      - Architectural Drawings, 2 18x16, 9 24x18, & 25 32x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details; outsized (Map-case 5)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Dr. Gerald A. Stair Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. Misc. 1960 Dr. and Mrs. Ingram Justin Kleaveland, Lot #3 Bear Lakes Shores, North Muskegon, MI, 1960
      - Architectural Drawings, 7 24x18-inch drawings; colored pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 66-61, Mr. and Mrs. Leslie A. Grimord, 19 Heatheridge Street, Ann Arbor, MI 1961
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 5)
        (see Job 48-59, Grimord)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 67-61, Mr. and Mrs. Larkin B. Breed 3493 W. Delhi Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1961
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 11.5 x9 & 29 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 68-61, Mr. and Mrs. Louis J. Richard 3101 Henry Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1961
      - Architectural Drawings, 10 24x18-inch drawings; colored pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 69-61, Mr. and Mrs. Haven H. Spencer 2465 Bedford Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1961
      - Architectural Drawings, 19 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 70-61, Professors Henry V.S. and Margaret Ogden 4475 Ford Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1961
      - Architectural Drawings, 27 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 71-61, Mr. Kyle L. Fuller, Office (Hodges Travel Agency) 2333 W. Stadium Boulevard, Ann Arbor, MI, 1961
      - Architectural Drawings, 17 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Presentation Board, 1 20x14-inch board; outsized (Map-case 13)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 72-61, Mr. and Mrs. Kenneth Davidson/Mr. and Mrs. Douglas S. Sherwin, Parkridge Drive/Barton Shore Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1961
      (designed, but not built, for Davidson; revised and built for Sherwin)
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 18x12, 2 14x11, & 28 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum, pencil on tissue paper; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. Misc. 1961 Mr. John Hall, 1715 Hermitage Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1961
      (alterations not built)
      - Architectural Drawings, 5 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; study; plans, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. Misc. 1961 Professor and Mrs. Rensis Likert, 14 Regent Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1961
      - Architectural Drawings, 4 24x-18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; plans, sections (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. Misc. 1961 Mr. and Mrs. Lewis A. Price, 837 1/2 East Comstock Street, Owosso, MI, 1961
      - Architectural Drawings, 2 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; rendering, plan (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. Misc. 1961 Professor Stephen O. Spurr, Lot #15, Highland Terrace Subdivision [880 Colliston], Ann Arbor, MI, 1961
      - Architectural Drawings, 5 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; plans (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Presentation Board, 1 26.5x19-inch board; outsized (Map-case 13)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 73-62, Island Park Shelter 1450 Island Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1962
      - Architectural Drawings, 15 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 74-62, Mr. Albert Duckek (II) 2901 Devonshire Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1962
      - Architectural Drawings, 26 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. and Mrs. John W. Martin Client File (Box 4)
        - Mr. David V. Ragone Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 75-62, Professor and Mrs. William L. Root 3451 Daleview Drive, Ann Arbor MI, 1962
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 18x12 & 24 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 76-62, Mr. and Mrs. Peter Van Boven, Jr., 6 Regent Court, Ann Arbor, MI 1962
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 18x12 & 47 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 77-62, Professor and Mrs. Stuart S. Churchill, 939 Forest Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1962
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 21x16 & 38 24x18-inch drawings; pen on vellum, pencil on vellum; study, rendering, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
    - Job No. 78-62, Dr. and Mrs. Edmund Krigbaum 3075 Overridge Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1962
      - Architectural Drawings, 2 21x16 & 51 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. Misc. 1962 Alpha Delta Pi (Werner), Sorority House, 722 S. Forest Avenue, Ann Arbor, MI, 1962
      - Architectural Drawings, 45 24x18 & 28 36x24-inch drawings; pencil on vellum, pencil on paper; plans, elevations, sections, details; outsized (Map-case 6)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Presentation Board, 1 23.5x16-inch board; outsized (Map-case 13)
    - Job No. Misc. 1962 Mr. and Mrs. Michael Radock, 2634 Devonshire Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1962
      - Architectural Drawings, 7 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 5)
    - Job No. 79-63, BBON Venture (Drs. Edmund S. Botch, Walter Belser, Charles W. Newton, & John A. O'Sullivan), Medical Office 2310 E. Stadium Boulevard, Ann Arbor, MI, 1963
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 21x12, 12 24x18, & 20 36x24-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum, pencil on paper; plans, elevations, sections, details; outsized (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 80-63, Drs. Theodore R. Cage and T.J. Smeckert, Dental Office 1820 Washtenaw Avenue, Ypsilanti, MI, 1963
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 21x11.5, 1 8x14, 1 21x14, 41 24x18, & 1 36x24-inch drawings; pencil on paper, pencil on tracing paper, pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide box 6)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Courtland Corporation (Box 5)
          (see Job 89-65 for drawings & client file)
    - Job No. 81-63, Mr. and Mrs. James E. Heywood, 19 Regent Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1963
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 14x6.5, 2 14x14, & 36 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide boxes 3 & 6)
    - Job No. 82-63, Attorney and Mrs. John R. Laird (I) 2445 Adare Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1963
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 22.5x 8, & 27 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide box 3)
    - Job No. 83-64, Dr. and Mrs. Walter H. Swartz 1120 Chestnut Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1964
      - Architectural Drawings, 2 21x15, 1 8x16, & 33 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on tracing paper, pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 6)
      - Client File (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. Hameedi Client File (Box 5)
    - Job No. 84-64, Professor and Mrs. John H. Holland (I) 3800 W Huron River Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1964
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 84-64, 109-83, 134-99, & 151-08, 1 21x11, 1 21x12.5, 1 21x14, 1 21x16, 1 21x17.5, & 61 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil and pen on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 7)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
      - Presentation Boards for Jobs 84-64 & 134-99, 2 11.5x9, 1 13x16.5, 1 18x13, & 1 24x18-inch boards; outsized (Map-case 13)
    - Job No. 85-64, Dr. and Mrs. William R. Mann 1329 Glendaloch Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1964
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 20.5x14 & 38 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 7)
      - Client File (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Dr. and Mrs. Vigen Darian (Box 5)
          (see Job 131-97 for drawings, client and graphics files, & photographs)
    - Job No. 86-64, Professor and Mrs. James Olds, 260 Indian River Place, Ann Arbor, MI 1964
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 86-64 & 129-96, 1 12x11, 1 11x12, 1 9.5x12, 3 12x12, 1 14x12, & 48 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum and tissue; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 7)
      - Client File (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Presentation Boards, 1 10x15, 1 16x13, & 4 30x20-inch boards; outsized (Map-case 14)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Professor and Mrs. Elliot Valenstein (Job 129-96) Client File (Box 5)
    - Job No. Misc. 1964 Phi Alpha Kappa (Werner), Fraternity House, 1010 E. Ann Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1964
      (addition not built)
      - Architectural Drawings, 10 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans (Map-case 7)
      - Client File (Box 5)
    - Job No. Misc. 1964 Professor and Mrs. Robert M. Warner (Werner), 1821 Coronada Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1964
      - Architectural Drawings, 3 21x18 & 5 24x18-inch drawings; pencil and pen on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 7)
        (see also Job Misc. 1974 Warner)
      - Client File (Box 5)
    - Job No. 87-65, Professor and Mrs. Richard A. Leabo 2424 Londonderry Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1965
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 87-65, 142-02, & 148-03, 1 11x8.5, 1 12x13, 10 21x5, & 47 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 7)
      - Client File (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Professor Jessy W. Grizzle & Dr. Laurie McCauley (Jobs 142-02 & 148-03) Client File (Box 5)
    - Job No. 88-65, Ms. Linda E. Eberbach 2249 Glendaloch Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1965
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 21x14.5 & 31 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 7)
      - Client File (Box 5)
      - Graphics File (Box 5)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. Neal Plotkin & Ms. Deborah Malamud Client File (Box 5)
    - Job No. 89-65, Courtland Corporation, Office 1820 Washtenaw Avenue, Ypsilanti, MI, 1965
      - Architectural Drawings, 19 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 7)
        (see also Job 80-63, Cage & Smeckert)
      - Client File (Box 5)
    - Job No. 90-65, Mr. and Mrs. Arjay R. Miller 2320 Devonshire Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1965
      (Mr. Mill was President of Ford Motor Company, May 1963-February 1968)
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 10x18 & 59 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pen on vellum, & pencil on vellum and paper; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 7)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Graphics Folder (Box 6)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 6)
        (see Box 11)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. Misc. 1965 Dr. and Mrs. Joseph J. Bookstein, 2659 Englave Drive, Ann Arbor, MI
      - Architectural Drawings, 4 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 7)
      - Client File (Box 6)
    - Job No. 91-65, Dr. and Mrs. Max L. Hutt, 21 Regent Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1966
      - Architectural Drawings, 39 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 7)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Graphics File (Box 6)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 92-66, Professor and Mrs. Keeve M. Siegel, 276 Indian River Place, Ann Arbor, MI 1966
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 14x8, 1 18x12, 37 24x18, & 25 36x24-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; pen on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details; outsized (Map-case 8)
      - Client File, 4 folders (Box 6)
      - Graphics File (Box 6)
      - Presentation Boards, 1 14x11 & 1 30x20-inch boards; outsized (Map-case 14)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide boxes 3 & 7)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Ms. Janette (Ferrantino) Williams Client File (Box 6)
        - Dr. and Mrs. Tadatka Yamada Client File (Box 6)
    - Job No. 93-66, Professor and Mrs. Guy E. Swanson, 305 Awixa Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1966
      - Architectural Drawings, 36 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pen and pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File (Box 6)
      - Graphics File (Box 6)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Dr. Robert Ellsworth Ireland Client File (Box 6)
    - Job No. 94-66, Professor Elmer Gilbert (I) 2659 Heatherway, Ann Arbor, MI, 1966
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 94-66 & 141-02, 1 12x9, 3 18x12, & 42 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Graphics File (Box 6)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
      - Presentation Boards, 1 9x11.754, 2 11.75x9, 1 12x8, 1 16.5x12.5, & 1 17x11-inch boards; outsized (Box 6)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. Misc. 1966 St. Luke's Lutheran Church, 4205 Washtenaw Avenue, Ann Arbor, MI, 1966
      - Architectural Drawings, 13 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File (Box 6)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. Misc. 1966 Dr. and Mrs. George J. Chatas (Werner), 2984 Hickory Lane, Ann Arbor, MI, 1966
      - Architectural Drawings, 41 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum & colored pencil on paper; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Job No. 95-67, Mr. Robert C. Metcalf, Office 2211 Medford Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1967
      - Architectural Drawings, 37 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File (Box 6)
      - Graphics File (Box 6)
      - Presentation Boards, 1 27x20 & 1 30x20-inch boards; outsized (Map-case 15)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 96-67, Drs. Ian and Millicent Higgins, 252 Indian River Place, Ann Arbor, MI 1967
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 96-67 & 114-88, 2 21x10.5, 1 21x11, 2 21x11.5, 1 21x12.5, 1 12x18, & 54 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; studies, rendering, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Graphics File (Box 6)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
      - Presentation Boards, 1 20x15-inch & 1 17x11-inch drawing; outsized (Map-case 15)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. Misc. 1967 Professor and Mrs. Donald J. Lewis, Lot #5 Block VIII, Barton Hills Subdivision (Oakdale Road), Ann Arbor, MI, 1967
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 21x12.5, 1 21x13, 1 21x18, 1 22x15, & 10 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections (Map-case 8)
      - Client File (Box 6)
      - Graphics File (Box 6)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. Misc. 1967 Professor James Wilkes, 1718 Sheridan Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1967
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 21x17 & 7 14x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections (Map-case 8)
      - Client File (Box 6)
    - Job No. 97-68, Towner Medical Building (Drs. William P. Edmunds, Lyle Elliott, Robert Fisher, George S. Sayre, Fulton B. Taylor, Paul J. Wicht, & Scott W. Woods), Office, 750 Towner Street, Ypsilanti, MI 1968
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 16x12, 1 22.5x14, & 60 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; study, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File, 3 folders (Box 6)
      - Graphics File (Box 7)
      - Presentation Board, 1 14x11-inch board; outsized (Map-case 15)
    - Job Nos. 98-68 & 99-68, Park Shelter and Bandstand, Bentley Park, Owosso, MI 1968
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 98-68 & 99-68, 25 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Box 7)
      - Client File (Box 7)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 100-68, Professor and Mrs. Erich E. Steiner, 268 Indian River Place, Ann Arbor, MI 1968
      - Architectural Drawings, 32 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevation, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File (Box 7)
      - Graphics File (Box 7)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
      - Presentation Board, 1 20x15-inch board (Map-case 15)
    - Job No. 101-69, Nu Sigma Nu, Fraternity House 1912 Geddes Avenue, Ann Arbor, MI, 1969
      (first designed for E. Huron Road; redesigned for Fuller Road; then redesigned and built at Geddes Avenue location)
      - Architectural Drawings, 89 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; studies, rendering, schematics, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File, 6 folders (Box 7)
      - Graphics File, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Presentation Boards, 1 15x12, 1 253/4x19, & 1 30x20-inch boards; outsized (Map-case 15)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 102-71, Mr. and Mrs. Allen L. Mayerson, 860 Colliston Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1971
      - Architectural Drawings, 42 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File (Box 7)
    - Job No. 103-71, Ecorse Medical Building (Drs. Parviz Meghnot, Alex E. Moyyad, John M. Moyyad, & Gerald A. Stair), Office, Ypsilanti, MI 1971
      - Architectural Drawings, 4 21x13, 1 21x14, 2 21x15, 1 21x 17.5, 1 23x17.5, & 26 24x18-inch drawings; brownline, blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 8)
      - Client File (Box 7)
    - Job No. Misc. 1971 Professor and Mrs. Harry Edwards, 1623 Granger Avenue, Ann Arbor, MI 1971
      - Architectural Drawings, 5 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 7)
    - Job No. Misc. 1971 University of Michigan, Lorch Hall, 611 Tappan Avenue, Ann Arbor, MI, 1971
      (office remodel)
      - Architectural Drawings, 2 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 7)
    - Job No. 105-74, Attorney and Mrs. John R. Laird (II) 3150 Hunting Valley Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1974
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 105-74 & 122-92, 1 7.5 x12, 1 10x12, 1 21x10, 1 21x11, 1 18x12, 6 21x12.5, 5 21x13, 2 21x14, 1 21x17, & 46 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on tracing paper & pen and pencil on vellum; schematics, rendering, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Graphics Folder (Box 7)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide box 4)
    - Job No. Misc. 1974 Mr. Erwin C. Paul, 7612 Lamb Road, Manchester, MI, 1974
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 21x15 & 5 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 7)
    - Job No. Misc. 1974 Professor and Mrs. Robert M. Warner (Werner), Lot #3 Surfwood, Friendship Township, MI, 1974
      (see also Job Misc. 1964 Warner)
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 15x14.5, 1 16x15, & 13 24x18-inch drawings; brownline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 7)
    - Job No. 106-75, Mr. and Mrs. George Huebner, 720 Oakdale Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1975
      (Mrs. Gertrude Huebner was a University of Michigan Regent, 1967-1975)
      - Architectural Drawings, 41 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; rendering, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Graphics File (Box 7)
      - Presentation Board, 1 17x11.5-inch board; outsized (Map-case 15)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide boxes 4 & 9)
    - Job No. 107-78, Dr. and Mrs. Eugene F. Claeys 3965 Penberton Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1978
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 21x14, 2 21x15, 1 21x18, & 38 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File (Box 7)
      - Graphics File (Box 7)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide boxes 4, 8, & 9)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Dr. Steven J. Bernstein & Dr. Maria Herrero Client File (Box 7)
    - Job No. 108-80, Dr. Stanley Watson and Dr. Huda Akil 3351 Windshadow Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1980
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 108-80, 123-93, 140-01, & 146-03, 1 12x12, 1 17x10, 1 18x12, 1 22.5x12, 1 21x15, 68 24x18-inch drawings; blueline & pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 9)
      - Client File, 6 folders (Box 8)
      - Graphics File (Box 8)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
      - Presentation Board, 1 13x19-inch board; outsized (Map-case 15)
      - Slides (Box 12)